Nice to meet you, we are
ENJOY PLAY! A playground for everyone! Gang Parade!
We are pleased to announce that Gang Parade
We are going to have a general election for different chapters!
Yay!
What's the different chapters general election?
The Gang Parade Election will be held this summer.
Last year, we held a general election for the songs in the FC tour for fan club members only.
We held a general election of songs.
We did it, didn't we?
We made a set list with the top songs from your ranking and the ranking that was made public.
We made a set list with the top ranked songs.
And then we went around the country.
It was a very hot
It was fun!
It was so much fun!
You can't hear it! There was one recently!
It's really rare.
It was a very special tour that you can only experience
It was a very special tour
This time it's not about the music
but with a general election of different chapters!
I'm so happy!
Gang Parade has a long history
We have done many different chapters in many different works.
but this time, we have 25 songs from all of them!
This time, we have 25 different chapters from all of them!
That's amazing!
From a total of 25 songs
I'm going to be playing 7 different works in 7 different places in the country this time.
The top 7 different chapters will be
We will wear them in each of the 7 places.
Yay!
The tour is starting!
We'll wear the top 7 sigils from the top 1 to the top 7.
You mean different ones for different parts of the country?
That's right!
This is bad!
We're going on a different tour all over the country!
Tsutsuuraurauraigurentein Grand Update
We are starting our 100th Night Tour!
Yay!
It's a yokai!
So here it is!
I'm going to be looking back at various different chapters as well.
I released in December 2016.
I started with the different chapters of Plastic to Mercy
I've also included a chapter of Goggio the Best Paradise, which was released in December 2016.
25 necklaces, including all of these outfits that I'm wearing this time.
This is also amazing!
This one is also included!
Enter!
I hope you all had a great time.
This tour is for fan club members only.
Please join our fan club if you want to join us!
Please join our fan club!
We have a lot of information about the competition.
I'm sure we'll have a lot to talk about.
I'm sure you'll hear about the various competitions and I'll look back on them.
If there is something you would like to try on, please let us know.
I do!
I'd like to hear all kinds of questions.
Maybe it will help the fans to vote.
I bet there are a lot of people who don't know about it.
That's for sure.
And last year's song general election was
I had a lot of people come backstage to vote for their favorite songs.
We had quite a few people backstage.
And the members were pretty vocal.
How the costumes looked like...
It might be big.
It might be loud again.
Let's look back, shall we?
Let's look back!
First of all, GANG PARADE 2016
The timing of the joining of Cocoyou Doxon
Covering Plastic 2 Macy's
Not a cover!
COVER!!!
What the hell are you doing Plastic 2 Mathy?
Re-recorded
We re-recorded the song in a 7-piece version.
This is the costume we wore when we released it.
SOTTY did the costumes for GANG PARADE's
SOTTY also worked on the costumes for GANG PARADE's office.
This was the first time for SOTTY to be involved in GANG PARADE
SOTTY worked on the costumes for GANG PARADE for the first time.
So it was our first time too.
It was our first time
It was the first time SOTTY worked on our costumes.
We were so happy.
And we all loved the flowers.
From a distance, they look like they have tattoos.
So stylish.
I got my first outfit.
I cried.
When I saw the paintings, I was so moved.When I saw the paintings, I got a big kick out of them.
It's for me, right?
The costumes.
Each member's name was written on it.
I remember I was so happy to see that I could get a costume
I remember I was so happy.
From here
Here are the costumes of HOWL.
This is pretty much
From the Plastic Joe Mancian costume
Howl and so on and so forth.
I'm pretty sure the word "Glentine" was coined.
GANG feeling
I think it was a time when the GANG feeling was strong.
I have that image.
GANG embroidered on the back of HOWL
Pig GANG
It's so cute!
I have an image of embroidery around this time of year.
I think there was a lot of embroidery around Shibuya.
Do you know? Have you seen it?
Have you seen it?
Of course I have.
Thank you.
I've seen you in front of this cat at Don Quijote.
You know, right?
That image.
The old Shibuya Donki.
It's closed now.
That's right.
Close by.
Across the street.
You can feel the history.
These are reversible, right?
Yes, they are.
Red.
Red
The red
The color of stupid.
I really like it live.
I want to wear it.
Really?
Actually, I'm fine with just a couple of reds.
If you do it like this, it'll be a little song.
A song.
Maybe during the MC's or something.
I'd like to wear it.
Each member has a different pair of underpants.
The underpants are actually different for each member.
When there are 13 of us.
That's true.
That's for sure.
Let's continue.
BEYOND THE MOUNTAIN
Yes, sir.
This is the outfit that Aya and Saki traded
Aya and Saki traded their outfits
It's also very frenetic.
Yes...
It's like a suicide suit.
That's why.
Embroidery.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's why the costumes for BEYOND THE MOUNTAIN
It has some kind of hood on it.
like a short disturbance.
It's cute.
like that.
The back looks like embroidery.
It makes the legs look longer.
That's right.
Like that.
I think they'll be popular.
Are those pink pants?
We're all wearing pink pants.
Isn't that unusual?
No, not at all.
And they're all the same shape, too.
They're the same color.
Same color.
They were all wearing pants.
But I didn't expect to see so many in pants at the beginning.
That's true.
Later on, there were a lot of skirts.
Yes, that's right.
Album
GANG PARADE
TENX
ZEMU
SELF
SAHAYA has been released
This one is also women's style.
The last one is quite like a suicide suit
A little bit menswear-like
but this time it's more like a sailor suit
but this time it's more like a sailor suit.I was pretty much in a sailor suit at this time.
A little bit of a female skeleton.
She's so cute.
I love this one so much.
I love it so much.
It's... it's... it's...
It's really popular.
So popular!
I knew GANG PARADE when I saw this outfit.
Really?
I have this image of them.
That's why GANG PARADE's music videos and stuff.
We filmed this.
That's definitely a GANG PARADE outfit.
We filmed them in their costumes, so it's pretty cool.
Embroidery?
And this.
It's my name.
It's a sailor suit.
This one is embroidered.
A baby?
A baby.
Boy.
I like that one too.
I'm cool too
I'm cool.
That's why
All the kanji characters are also
I'm so glad you put them in azue characters.
Maybe we won't get to see this.
I'm looking forward to it.
Possibilities.
Or infinity.
Amazing.
Love
Summer
What's summer?
Love
Summer Star
Cool.
Love
Summer star
Nice.
Awesome.
mugwort
I think it's really cool.
I think so, I think so.
It's nice, isn't it?
Love it.
Summer star
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm getting paranoid.
So I'm fine with this.
When it comes to embroidery.
That's another point of interest.
Love
Natsunoshi.
What do you think?
I think a lot of members like it.
Ai
Is this Tsuki?
Tsuki
I want to come.
Certainly the moon too.
I've never worn one myself.
That's why.
Well, well, well.
But you said you liked this one too, right?
She was wondering if it was beauty or tastes.
I'm really torn.
That's why I want you to put it in... both.
I really want you to put them in.
And the last part of the trade.
I'd like to see you in the last outfit of the trade.
Here.
What? What?
The gang.
Here, gangster.
Embroidery.
Embroidery on the lining.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like this.
embroidery on the lining of the jacket.
and there's a belly, too.
Cute
raw momochan
It's pretty much from around here.
What do you call it?
Bicolor?
I've been seeing a lot of skirts with a lot of different colors in them.
are becoming more and more common.
It's a bit like gangster curry.
Skirts and pants are divided, aren't they?
That's for sure.
But look at this.
She's wearing a gold necklace.Wear the time with a gold necklace.
It's a costume, so the gold kimono is on the neck and sleeves.
It's definitely gold.
It's amazing.
It's so nice.
It's so beautiful.
That's why I thought I'd be a bit of a jerk until the trade.
It's a bit of a rush.
I'd like to come back for a more forceful one.
That's for sure.
Gangsterish.
It's been a while.
I've had more of a parade feel since I was 13 years old.
Certainly a gangster feel.
And this Arthur guy is really messed up.
That too...
It's like Satei said in his comment here...
The next Gang 2 is coming out.
It's more of a parade than a gang.
It's true.
I heard there's a theme.
I've heard that there's a theme to it.
Seki said that the year 2018...
Here we go!
Gang 2.
Did you see this?
No, I see it.
I know.
I mean, these outfits, they're... they're unusual.
They're all the same.
They're all in one piece.
It's unusual, that's for sure.
And they have hoods.
I had it on at the time of Gangster 2.
But the first time I did Gangster 2, I put the hood on.
I'm gonna put a mustache on it.
So I'd like to do Gang 2 with this outfit.
It's so good.
I want to do this costume so bad.
I can't go back out in costume.
That's so good.
I want to do Gang 2 in this outfit so bad.
I'll see you then.
I'll talk to you about it.
You know what surprised me at first?
The skirts are all the same length.
That's right.
They're all different heights.
That's amazing.
And yet the skirts are the same length.
We're going to start gang 2 in a row.
And when they're all lined up side by side
The skirts are the same length.
It's amazing.
You could do more handstands.
Even if you kahn back or something.
It looks so beautiful.
Next...
Cant stop
I like this one too.
I love this one.
I've been saying all along
I've always said I love cant stops.
I love this one.
It's a horizontal connection that goes on and on.
It's like a cant-stop.
Isn't it nice?
On this skirt.
There's a riber in the skirt.
Isn't it nice?
I don't often put borders in my dresses.
It's a different color.
The color scheme.
Especially.
It's very informal.
It was very easy to move around.
Yeah, it was.
It was easy to move around.
It was very easy to move around.
Very easy to move around.
I love it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Expectations.
And the same year we put out
The last indie
That's it.
The last indie album
It came out at the end of the year.
Last Gang Parade
I'll take it.
This is it
If you don't go out, you'll go home
The color is different too
Yes, yes
It's colorful, too.
It's like a gang parade.
It also has a hood.
A lot of them have hoods.A lot of them have hoods on them.
This time of year.
That's true.
There were a lot of them.
Depending on the member's color
The color of the sleeve is different depending on the member's color.
The color of the sleeve is the member's color, and the name is on it.
the name on it.
in English.
Like a rontie.
When we
when we were putting it on the gupin.
I'm glad it has my name on it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it's a really special costume.
And when there are 13 of us...
The arms are so colorful.
So cute.
Cute.
The colors are so cute.
That's nice.
Maybe we'll get another break here.
That's a lot.
Yes, it is.
Major from here.
I've been a major player in
Brand new parade
Costumes for the Brand New Parade
I'm quite attached to this one, too.
The letters...
The gangsters...
You know...
You said a lot of things, didn't you?
They're different.
The gangs are all arranged differently.
That's why they look alike.
They look like one person.
But when you look closely, they're all different.
That's why there are more types.
I like Sokki-'s comment
I'm trying to keep the colors elegant.
If it were a major player...
It's true
Colorful, but...
It's just...
It's colorful.
It's a little bit...
In the back.
Red.
Curtains.
It's really nice.
So there.
This is the end of the
Challenge the Limit Tour
Hibiya Nohe
It was an unveiling.
Naruha will be here
In May of 2019
Naruha joined us in May 2019.
I'm going to show you
It's a very
Special
Only for the
It's only for 12 concerts.
Only 12, right?
There aren't many other costumes that are only worn for one day.
There aren't many others.
That's true.
I went once for the Fall Foliage Festival.
Really.
We went to a concert.
Yes.
The live concert was really in the field, too.
Mr. America's costume
I like this.
The cape.
Yes, the tone of YuYuYu.
I want this.
So.
This one has a cape.
Cute.
It's cute.
And the shoes.
They're cute.
They were cute.
And...
The music and the game create magic
Majikami
Yes, Majikami.
We had a tie-up with a music company.
and I was able to release a lot of stuff at the time.
a little bit like a game
Cool outfit
Combat uniform
I like this one too.
I like this one.
This one is cute.
I like this one too.This one is cute too.
I love Naruha.
This is so cool!
I don't know...
I didn't even have a pants outfit.
That's for sure.
This one was pretty cool, too.
It was cool.
Okay. And the next one...
Love Parade.
Oh, my gosh!
First full album.
I want to wear this
Congratulations!
I love the way you look in this outfit
I really like the visual of Tsuki in this outfit.
I know what you mean.
So when you get into this outfit...
I'm going to give you bright red makeup.
Bright red.
You know, that time...
Remix.
Yeah, bright red.
It's kind of pinkish.
It was so colorful.
And then all of a sudden, it just went straight.
All of us
And our feelings...
We're all...
We all went quiet.
We all seemed a little more relaxed.
It's true, this one's a little less different.
That's true.
Even when you look at them side by side.
But this...
Ms. I wonder again...
Ten years old.
We'll talk about it later.
It's all connected, child.
Yes, sir.
So...
It's all white, but we're all...
Different materials...
Yes, yes.
And shapes.
Different colors
Amazing.
And the Parade Gozon 2?
Yes, sir.
It's a parade in the name of a parade.
It's already marching!
This is cool.
The marching.
That's cool.
This is cool.
It's so cute.
What about the instruments?
You're not coming with me?
The instruments don't follow us.
I'm not following you.
Why don't you just wear the hat?
If they pick me for this.
I'd definitely do it.
I'll do it.
It's gonna mess up the music.
What's going on in your head?
I didn't do that one song.
We only did those three songs.
When I was carrying them in.
In my hat.
Nara Hana's hat was in my hat.
That's right.
I put Narahana's hat in my hat.
My hat.
That's great!
And now it's 2020.
I unveiled it on New Year's Day for the first time in the new year.
of the Limina stage.
Felicea Teas's costume
This one has also changed quite a bit
Stylish.
This is cool.
It's a bit warlike.
I want to wear this.
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
But I think I kind of like it.
I really like it.
I have to say it.
To the fans.
It comes with a bag.
Can I have a tie, please?
There's a lot of parts.
If I forget something, I'll be in trouble.
I'm in tears. I forgot a part.
Here's something else.
Five parts.
Straight 1
You're not going to wear it now.You're not supposed to wear it now.
The first one.
I want to forget something in the fifth.
Oh!
I'm gonna forget something.
But you know what, that's really great, too.
I have a great image of it.
I know, I know.
It was special, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
It's so cute.
I'd love to wear it... with the 13 of us.
Yeah, I'd like that.
I'd love to.
I mean, it was my last outfit before the split.
That one.
From here on out.
Yes, ma'am.
Gang Parade split.
Yes.
Mozart to Baradice precipice
Rush
We're going in!
GP Costume
G and P split costume
Each other's body halves
Although they are wearing each other's costumes
One is in a color scheme of the other
The design of one of them
Half of the design is on one side
Gray.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's amazing... the attention to detail is amazing.
That's why it's...
It's not quite the same, but...
It fits together.
We're all in this together.
And if there are 13 of us...
What will we be?
This is the most complicated.
That's not it.
It's all gray.
Ehhhh...
Because... there are four colors.
Could it be...
Because Saki-san's wearing it.
Because, you see, I'll be with Saki-san
G4
I thought there were a lot of them.
It's classified.
So my fault is now gray.
Gray.
That's funny.
Gray. That's funny.
That's Maybo.
Maybo.
Maeve, in case you're wondering.
I've worn a meibo.
I've never worn it.
I don't have a costume.
Oh, I see.
I don't have a meibo.
No meibo.
We've all passed the test before.
Yes, we have.
That's why when we split up...
You were there.
You know, Maybo...
A lot.
Later.
A lot of meibo.
A lot of meibos.
Here, take this.
It's their costumes.
I had them put them together.
So, it's a little bit of both.
Both of them.
You know, Saki...
The "both" one.
Both are difficult.
This outfit looks tough.
Oh, no, no, no...
I was just voting to see how it would turn out.
That's why I voted, to see what would happen.
You're right.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
But I'll tell you this.
With this...
The only time I've ever performed live in this costume
Only at Nakano-san Plaza
That's right.
It's a very rare costume.
I'm sure you'll get a chance to wear it.
Maybe...
Maybe you'll be able to see it.
And you know what?And.
From here.
We're going to have a BP split.
Well, first of all...
Let's start with the Gauchers.
Erin, you're wearing an angel costume.
So...
Um... Makami...
Um...
By Gauchers.
I was allowed to do it...
At that time...
Did you get BP?
No, not yet.
Not yet.
Yes, just before.
That's why you want to come.
No.
No BP.
Not at all
I want to come!
I want to come to Rags to Riches.
So first...
Like a pretty maid
I was doing it! I was doing it!
The one I cheated on you with.
Wow.
And then I was like, "Oh, my God, I'm falling apart.
That's pretty cute, too.
But it's so cool.
I mean, that outfit...
BP always wanted to come in that one.
He wanted to wear yellow.
It's a bit of a member color.
Yeah, member colors.
New member colors.
Yeah, that's right.
That's the first time I've ever seen them in yellow.
I think that might have been my first time.
I just want to come over.
I want to come a little bit.
That's why they're all in shabby colors.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's totally different.
Not even close.
I want to come here.
I want to come here, please, please, please.
What are you going to wear?
Let's just keep the grizzly.
No, but...
But... since we're here...
I'm a little beat up.
It's just me and this one... in shreds.
They're all so thick.
I like the ragged ones.
Rags and tatters, saves me the trouble.
So, BP's been coming to me ever since I joined.
I've always wanted to come in this one.
This is what BP is wearing this time around.
This is the one I want the most!
Heh.
And around the same time
This one?
Hey, P-pop!
Yes, sir.
BP is good
There's a good costume.
This one started out blue.
No capes.
That's right.
And then later on, they had capes.
The posture changed a little bit.
This is the costume that we wore at some point.
When Cannon joined the group.
Yeah, it was red when it came out.
When it came to this...
What was it, red?
Or is it...
But no.
They didn't have blue fabric, so it became red.
Maybe they already have it.
Maybe we can get you some blue.
Well, then I'll go with red.
I'm going to go with blue.
I want to wear this outfit.
It's so cute, isn't it?
I want to wear it, too.
I want a new outfit, too.
You're right.
How many do you want?
You want to wear something you've never worn before.
It's not the only one.
It's the only one.
We're the only ones, by the way.
Maybe there's four of us.
Then I want to wear it.
It's the only one.
Because everyone else is wearing it.Because other people are wearing it.
That's it.
Because I'm already wearing my costume.
Then you're wearing it.
You still don't look blue.
Or maybe...
I cut it in half again.
Blue.
I love this outfit.
It's cute.
But you're right.
They're all so cute when they come out.
If you like it, you don't want to wear a cape yet.
I didn't have a cape on when I wore it.
I see.
But you do now.
You're right. I haven't seen a light blue cape.
That's for sure.
It was on when Lennon came in.
He got there.
And then the next.
I'd say it was about time.
Cannon.
I was just in front of Prislis Poo.
I was talking about when I joined.
Baby...
BLOOD COMPACT 2nd EP GO TO THE BEDS
The costumes...
Shinome's role.
Baby joined BLOOD COMPACT
Costume
So it's called "BLOOD COMPACT".
She said she was playing Shinome.
I thought, "I don't know, I don't feel like it.
He's so cool!
He looks like Katchu.
He was dressed like a Katchoo.
I've done this a hundred times.
That's right.
We've been around a hundred times.
I have a memory.
That's all the costumes.
Yes, we've done this about a hundred times.
These three outfits.
These outfits.
The red cape.
On her hips.
It's cute.
Some of them look like they're smeared with blood or something.
It looks like it's smeared all over the cab or something.
I can dodge the blood.
It looks like it's smeared.
It's a different color.
Yeah, only the blood was a different color.
That's funny.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, it is.
I have such fond memories of that.
When Baby was in the show.
That's the outfit when we became six.
And
The GET AWAY tour.
And our costumes.
The costumes for our most important songs.
And when we traded later
I'm going to trade for these costumes.
I'm going to trade them...
What do you think of our precious song?
This is also amazing.
The image of P's costume
I love it!
I love this one.
I already have this one.
I can't stand this one.
I got some great college photos at this time!
With a flat coater.
I'm sure of it. I'm sure of it.
When we were trading.
We were saying how nice it was when we traded.
Cut the first line and wear yellow.
School kids will come to England.
It's a sunshade!
It's so cute!
That's what I'm going to wear from now on.
All 13 of us.
It's gonna be costumes.
Even on New Year's Day.
These costumes.
I got to wear both the P and G costumes.
I got to wear both costumes.
The G costume has a belt around the waist
has a belt around the waist.
Brave man
It also has a hood.
Stylish.
The brave man
Beauty.I'm doing beauty.
This is so stylish.
It really is.
I'm sure each of them will change their outfits and stuff.
When it comes to this...
Everyone wears it.
They only wear it on New Year's.
It's also rare.
That's why they're so popular.
If there was a 7th one
I want to wear the G and P costumes.
I'd like to wear it
Please vote for a good one.
The big one
So...
GO TO THE BED PARADISE
The period of division is
is over here and we are
Restart
Here it comes!
Finally restart
The costumes from the restart
I guess there are five if you include this one.
So there are five if you include this one.
That's right.
The Parade Go Zone...
Ten of them.
On the contrary, three of them
They'll be costumes.
They'll be in costumes.
I'd like to see that, too.
I want to wear pants in this costume.
I want to wear pants.
I'm serious.
It makes me look good.
This is based on a costume from the Parade Go Zone tour.
The colors are similar.
They used red and blue.
And the shape is pretty much the same as back then.
It's similar.
And the connections.
It's interesting to see it now.
I did it before the last gang parade and the split.
I took over from the last tour.
I'm told that you gave them a great deal of guidance.
It's going to be a very memorable costume.
And from now on
We're going to have 13 members now.
Finally.
Naruho is back.
SEINAS joined the band
The first single
SIGNAL
It's been a long time since I've heard this one.
It's been a long time.
So cute!
Your comment
It's like a big family living deep in the mountains with more and more members.
Like a big family
Living deep in the mountains
Family of body
Body Family Theme
Taken deep in the mountains
That was fun.
It's colorful.
The next priority was to turn it around.
Chic
So pretty.
Love this one too.
Love Parade
Just like the Love Parade when it was all white before the split.
I used additional black fabric
to make the outfit more expressive.
To preserve the femininity
shoulders are exposed.
It's out.
Please help me.
Femininity.
I really liked the white outfit.
But it's interesting that there's a black outfit that's the complete opposite.
Interesting.
And I love
everyone loves it!
Love Parade Maid Costume
I'm looking forward to it.
Might be my last chance to see a maid costume.
That's for sure.
A lot of people liked the maids.
I was so nervous at first.
Everyone was pretty squeamish.
At the Gan Tan concert.
I was in the last block.
They said she was cute.
I'm using it as a motif for me and Roboko's maid.
It's a maid outfit.
This is one of my favorite costumes.
I love it.
It's really cute.
I love them all.
I'll be in the raft.I'm going out on the raft.
The last one is like this.
The 25th and last one is this.
They're really cute.
All 13 of them are different.
Seriously.
Even the shoes are different.
For the first time.
I think you can tell by repeating it.
Each person's outfit is so different.
This is the first time.
I'm really happy to show off the costumes on the line cab.
It's a really cool costume.
I hope you'll all sit down and have a seat.
Please have a seat!
Thank you very much!
So, that's it.
Summer is here.
I'm sure you're all looking forward to it.
Gang Parade official fan club
From Glentine's Renewal Cheering Group
Tsutsu Taura
The 100th anniversary of the Greatest Renewal of Glentine's
It has been decided to hold
Hokkaido on January 22nd
Obiiro
Obiiro.
This is pretty much the first time
for the first time
Outside Sapporo
This is my first time outside of Sapporo, Hokkaido.
I can do it.
That's right.
Starting from Obiiro on July 22nd
August 8 in Aichi
Diamond Hall
August 11 Fukuoka Drum Logos
August 13th Osaka Number Hatch
August 20, Penny Lane, back again in Hokkaido
Sapporo.
2 times
August 22nd at Tokyo Zep Diver
And the final show will be
August 25th in Miyagi
Sendai Chain
It was so much bigger than last year
I was in a great mood.
Everyone can really come.
You can all come.
Last tour...
I mean, it wasn't a madhouse, but...
I felt like I couldn't come.
Thankfully, it was pretty much a continuation of the Prime Minister's.
I think we can get a lot of people to come this time.
I'm sure we'll be able to get a lot of people to come this time.
I'm sure details will be announced at a later date
Please apply!
Thank you very much.
Well then, everyone!
I'd like to know what Young Parade will be wearing
What costume will Young Parade wear?
It's up to you to decide what costume the Young Parade will wear.
Wow.
We'll be wearing different costumes for all seven shows.
So please vote for us!
Please cast your votes!
Please vote!
We'll be able to tour!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to it.
We're looking forward to it!
That's all for us.
We're all having fun
Young Parade.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
That one.
Push! Push! Push!